<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>techiguana</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on techiguana</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 19:42:14 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>10 Smart Home Gifts for this Holiday Season</title>
      <link>/posts/2020/11/02/holiday-smart-home-gifts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 19:42:14 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2020/11/02/holiday-smart-home-gifts/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;With the holiday season quickly approaching, you are probably deep in your search for gifts to buy friends and loved ones. With smart home devcies quickly becoming a standard in many households, look no further. Here are 10 smart home devices that will not break the bank and are sure to make anyones Holiday Season special.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Turn Your TV Into a Smart TV</title>
      <link>/posts/2020/11/02/cheap-smart-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 19:42:14 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2020/11/02/cheap-smart-tv/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There are a multitude of options and products to help turn your standard television into a &amp;ldquo;smart&amp;rdquo; television without digging deep into your savings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With streaming services such as: &lt;a href=&#34;https://netflix.com&#34;&gt;Netflix&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://hulu.com&#34;&gt;hulu&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://hbo.com/ways-to-get&#34;&gt;HBO&lt;/a&gt; becoming more and more popular, the need for a smart TV is rising &amp;hellip; and quickly. Although companies like &lt;a href=&#34;https://samsung.com&#34;&gt;Samsung&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://vizio.com&#34;&gt;Vizio&lt;/a&gt; make great products, they come at a high pricepoint. Trust me, there are other options.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>techiguana At techiguana we are dedicated to making tech blogging and product reviews easier for you. We have adopted a less is more attitude and will strive to keep our blogs and reviews easy to read, clear, and consise.
Be sure to make use of the light/dark mode, depending on your preferences. The toggle is located in the top right. 😃
Big thanks to panr for his Hugo theme!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
